A Guide to the Plats and certificates of the Virginia Land Office, 1779-1982
Library of Virginia
- 1793
  - Ce-Cl, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Co-Con, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Coo-Coy, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Cr, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Cu, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Dab-Day, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Davidson, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Davies, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Davis, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - De, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Di, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Do, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Donnell, John, and Robert, James, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Dr-Du, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Duvall, John P., 1793. (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Duvall, John P., 1793. (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Dysart, James, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - E, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Fa, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Fe-Fl, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Fo-Fra, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Fre-Fu, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Ga, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Gi-Go, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Gr, 1793. (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Ha-Han, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Har, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Hat-Haz, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - He, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Hi, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Ho, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Hu, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - I, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Ja-Je, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Johnston-Ju, 1793. (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Ka-Ke, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Ki-Ky, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - La, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Le-Li, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Lo-Ly, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Mad-Mars, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Mart-Max, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Madison, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - McC, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - McD-McR, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Me-Mi, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Mof-Moo, 1793. (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Mor-Moy, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Mu-My, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Na-Ne, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Ni-No, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Oc-Ol, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - On-Oz, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Pa, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Pea-Pei, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Pen-Pel, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Ph-Pi, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Pl-Po, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Pra-Pre, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Pri-Pru, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Pu, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Ra-Rei, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Rel-Rey, 1793. (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Ri, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Ro, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Ru, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Sa-Se, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Sh, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Si-Sl, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Sm, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Sn-Sp, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Sta-Sto, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Stewart, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Str-Stu, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Su, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Sw-Sy, 1793. (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Ta, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Te, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Th-Ti, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Thompson, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - To-Tr, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Tu-Ty, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - U-Va, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Ve-Vi, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Wad-Wall, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Walt-Wat, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - We, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Wh, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Wi, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Williams, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Williamson, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Willson-Wilson, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Wo-Wr, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Y, 1793. (Box 123, Folder 18)
- 1794
  - A, 1794. (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Ba-Ber, 1794. (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Banks, Henry, 1794. (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Bi-Bo, 1794. (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Br-Bu, 1794. (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Ca-Ce, 1794. (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Ch-Cl, 1794. (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Co, 1794. (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Cr-Cy, 1794. (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Da-Di, 1794. (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Deakins, Francis and William, 1794. (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Do-Dy, 1794. (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - E, 1794. (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - F, 1794. (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Ga-Go, 1794. (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Gr-Gw, 1794. (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Ha, 1794. (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - He-Hi, 1794. (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Ho, 1794. (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Hu-Hy, 1794. (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - I-J, 1794. (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Ka-Ke, 1794. (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Ki-Ku, 1794. (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - La-Ll, 1794. (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Lo-Ly, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - McC, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - McD-McW, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Mac-Mar, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Ma-Me, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Mi, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Mo, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Moore, Samuel, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Mu, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - N, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - O, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Pa, 1794. (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Pe, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Ph-Pi, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Pr-Pu, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Ra-Re, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Ri-Ru, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Sa-Se, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Sh-Sk, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Sm-Sp, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - St-Sy, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Ta-Ti, 1794. (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - To-Ty, 1794. (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - U-V, 1794. (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Wa, 1794. (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - We, 1794. (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Wh-Wi, 1794. (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Wo-Wy, 1794. (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Y-Z, 1794. (Box 129, Folder 7)
- 1795
  - A, 1795. (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Abernathy, James, 1795. (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Ba-Be, 1795. (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Banks, Henry (Greenbrier Co.), 1795. (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Banks, Henry (Harrison Co.), 1795. (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Banks, Henry (Montgomery Co.), 1795. (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Bi-Bo, 1795. (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Br, 1795. (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Bu, 1795. (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Cab-Cal, 1795. (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Cam-Cay, 1795. (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Ce-Ch, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Cl, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Co, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Cr, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Cu, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Da-De, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Di, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Do-Dy, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - E, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - F, 1795. (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Ga-Ge, 1795. (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Gi-Go, 1795. (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Gr-Gu, 1795. (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Had-Han, 1795. (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Har-Hay, 1795. (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - He-Hi, 1795. (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Ho, 1795. (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi, 1795. (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Hu, 1795. (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - I, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - J, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Ka-Ke, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Ki-Ky, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - La, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Le, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Li-Ly, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - McA-McCl, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - McCo-McH, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - McK-McV, 1795. (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Mab-Mars, 1795. (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Mart-Maz, 1795. (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Maund, John James, 1795. (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Me, 1795. (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Mi, 1795. (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Mo-Mu, 1795. (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Morris, Robert, 1795. (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - N, 1795. (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - O, 1795. (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Pa, 1795. (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Pe, 1795. (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Ph-Pi, 1795. (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Po-Pu, 1795. (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Q, 1795. (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Ra-Re, 1795. (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Ri, 1795. (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Ro-Ru, 1795. (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Sa-Se, 1795. (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Sh-Sl, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Sm, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Richard, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Sn-Sp, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - St-Sw, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Ta-Te, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Th-Tu, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - V, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Wad-Wal, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - War-Wat, 1795. (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - We, 1795. (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Wh-Williams, 1795. (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Wilson-Wit, 1795. (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Wo-Wy, 1795. (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Yeiser, Frederick, 1795. (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Yo, 1795. (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Z, 1795. (Box 137, Folder 7)
- 1796
  - Aa-Ag, 1796. (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Al-An, 1796. (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Ap-Au, 1796. (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Bag-Barc, 1796. (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Barn-Bax, 1796. (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Banks, Henry, 1796. (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Bec-Bel, 1796. (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Ben-Bev, 1796. (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Bi-Bl, 1796. (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Bob-Bou, 1796. (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Bow-Boz, 1796. (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Br, 1796. (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Buc-Bur, 1796. (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Burn-By, 1796. (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Cab-Cal, 1796. (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Cam-Carp, 1796. (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Carr-Cas, 1796. (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Ch, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Cl, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Cob-Coo, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Cop-Cox, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Cr-Cu, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Dad-Davidson, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Davis-Day, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Deakin, Francis and William, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Dea-Dee, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Den-Dew, 1796. (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Di, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Dob-Dou, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Dov-Dow, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Dr-Dy, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - D - unidentified, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Ea, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Ed-Ep, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Er-Ew, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Fa, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Fe, 1796. (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Fi, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Fields, Nathan, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Fl, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Fo, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Fr, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Fu, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Gal, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Gam-Gay, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Ge-Gi, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Gl-Go, 1796. (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Gra, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Gre-Greenlee, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Greenup-Gru, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Gu-Gw, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - G - unidentified, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Hac-Hal, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Ham-Han, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Hark-Harp, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Harr-Hay, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - He, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Hi, 1796. (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Hog-Hook, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Hoope-Hou, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Hopkins, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - How-Hoz, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Hud-Hul, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Hum-Hy, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - I, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Ja-Je, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Joh, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Jon-Ju, 1796. (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Ke, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Kil-King, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Kinison-Kr, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - La, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Lea-Lem, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Les-Lew, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Li, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Loc-Lou, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Lov-Ly, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - McA-McClo, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - McClu, 1796. (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - McCo-McCr, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - McCu-McD, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - McF-McG, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - McH-McR, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Mac-Mar, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Mas-Maz, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Me, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Mi, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Mon-Moore, 1796. (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Mor-Mou, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Mu-My, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Na, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Ne, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Ni, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - No, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - O, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Pa-Patterson, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Patteson-Pax, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Pec-Pen, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Per-Pew, 1796. (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Ph-Pl, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Po, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Pr-Pu, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Q, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Ra, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Rea-Reedy, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Reese-Rey, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Rh-Ri, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Roa-Rob, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Rod-Roy, 1796. (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Ru, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Sa, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Sc, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Se, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Sha-She, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Shi-Si, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Sk-Sl, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Smiley-Smith, Joseph, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Samuel-Smyth, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Sn, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - So-Sp, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Sta, 1796. (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Stea-Stee, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Step-Stew, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Sti-Stu, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Su-Sy, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Ta, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Te, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Th-Ti, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - To-Ty, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - U, 1796. (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - V, 1796. (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Wad-Wallace, 1796. (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Waller-Wam, 1796. (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Ward-Warr, 1796. (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Wart-Wat, 1796. (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - We, 1796. (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Wh, 1796. (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Wia-Willey, 1796. (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Williams, 1796. (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, 1796. (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Wim-Wit, 1796. (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Wol-Woo, 1796. (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Woods, Archibald-James, 1796. (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Woods, John - Work, 1796. (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Wr-Wy, 1796. (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Ya-Young, James, 1796. (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Young, Joseph-Samuel, 1796. (Box 152, Folder 8)
- 1797
  - Aa-Ald, 1797. (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - All-An, 1797. (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Ar-Ay, 1797. (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Ba, 1797. (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Banks, Henry, 1797. (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Bea-Benner, 1797. (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Benoist-Bev, 1797. (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Bi-Bl, 1797. (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Bo, 1797. (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Br, 1797. (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Bu-By, 1797. (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Cab-Cam, 1797. (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Can-Ces, 1797. (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Ch-Cl, 1797. (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Claiborne, Richard, 1797. (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Coc-Coll, 1797. (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Colw-Cox, 1797. (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Cra, 1797. (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Cre-Cru, 1797. (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Cu, 1797. (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Da, 1797. (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - De, 1797. (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Di, 1797. (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Do, 1797. (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Dr-Dy, 1797. (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Ea-Ed, 1797. (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Ei-En, 1797. (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Er-Ev, 1797. (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Ew-Ey, 1797. (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Fa-Fi, 1797. (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Fl-Fo, 1797. (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Fr-Fu, 1797. (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Ga-Gi, 1797. (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Gl-Go, 1797. (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Gr-Gu, 1797. (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Ha-Harrison, 1797. (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Harrow-Hay, 1797. (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - He, 1797. (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Hi, 1797. (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Hob-Hook, 1797. (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Hooker-Hox, 1797. (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Hu-Hy, 1797. (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - I, 1797. (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Ja-Je, 1797. (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - John-Johnson, 1797. (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Johnston-Ju, 1797. (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Ke, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Kic-King, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - King, William - Kn, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - La, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Le, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Li, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Lo, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Lu-Ly, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - McCa-McCl, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - McCo-McG, 1797. (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - McI-McN, 1797. (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Ma, 1797. (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Me-Mi, 1797. (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Mol-Moo, 1797. (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Mor-Mos, 1797. (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Mu, 1797. (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - N, 1797. (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - O, 1797. (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Pa, 1797. (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Pe, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Ph-Pl, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Po, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Pr-Pu, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Q, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Ra, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Re, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Ri, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Ro-Ru, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Sa-Se, 1797. (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Sh-Sk, 1797. (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Smiley-Smith, Robert, 1797. (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Samuel-Snodgrass, 1797. (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - So-Sp, 1797. (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Sta-Ste, 1797. (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Sti-Stu, 1797. (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Su-Sw, 1797. (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Taa-Taylor, Isaac, 1797. (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, James-Te, 1797. (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Th-Tr, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Tu, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - V, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Wal-Warren, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Warrick-Wat, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - We, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Welch, James, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Welch James, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Wh, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Whitcroft, William, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Whitcroft, William, 1797. (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Wi, 1797. (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Wireman, Christian, 1797. (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Wireman, Christian, 1797. (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Wol-Wooding, 1797. (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Woods-Worr, 1797. (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Wr-Wy, 1797. (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Y, 1797. (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Z, 1797. (Box 163, Folder 8)
- 1798
  - Ad-Al, 1798. (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - An-Ay, 1798. (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Ba, 1798. (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Banks, Henry, 1798. (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Banks, Henry, 1798. (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Be-Bi, 1798. (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Bl, 1798. (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Bo, 1798. (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - Br, 1798. (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Bu-By, 1798. (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Cal-Cam, 1798. (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Car-Ce, 1798. (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Ch-Ci, 1798. (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Cl, 1798. (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Cloyd, 1798. (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Co, 1798. (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Cr, 1798. (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Cu, 1798. (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Da, 1798. (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - De-Di, 1798. (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Do, 1798. (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Dr-Dy, 1798. (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - E, 1798. (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Fa-Fl, 1798. (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - Fo-Fu, 1798. (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Ga-Gl, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Go-Gra, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Gre-Gw, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Ha-Hairston, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Hailey-Hall, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Ham-Harr, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Hart-Hay, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - He, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Hi, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Hog-Hol, 1798. (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - Hoo-How, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Hu-Hy, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - I, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Jam-Joh, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Jones, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Ke, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Ki, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - King, William, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - King, William, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - Kn-Ky, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - La, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Le, 1798. (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - Li-Lo, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Lu-Ly, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - McC, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - McD-McV, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Mad-Mar, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Mas-Maz, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Me-Mi, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Mon-Morg, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Morr-Mos, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Mu, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - N, 1798. (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - O, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Pa-Patten, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Patterson-Patton, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Pe, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Ph-Pi, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Pl-Po, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Pr-Pu, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Q, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Ra-Re, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Rh-Ri, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Ro, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Ru-Ry, 1798. (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - Sa-Se, 1798. (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Sh-Si, 1798. (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Sk-Sm, 1798. (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Sn-Sp, 1798. (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Sta-Ste, 1798. (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Sti-Sy, 1798. (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Ta-Te, 1798. (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Th-Ti, 1798. (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - To, 1798. (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - Tr-Tu, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - U, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - V, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Wad-Wal, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - War-Wat, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - We, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Wh, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Wilk-Wilsford, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Wilson-Wit, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - Wireman, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Wo-Wr, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Y, 1798. (Box 172, Folder 12)
- 1799
  - Ad-Al, 1799. (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - An-Ay, 1799. (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Ba, 1799. (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Be, 1799. (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Bi-Bl, 1799. (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Bo, 1799. (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Br, 1799. (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Bu-By, 1799. (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Cad-Cam, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Cap-Caz, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Ce-Ch, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Cl, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Cob-Con, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Coo-Cow, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Cro-Cu, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Cra, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Da, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - De, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Di-Do, 1799. (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Du-Dy, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Ea-Ed, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - El-Ew, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Fa-Fl, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Fo-Fr, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Ga, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Ge-Gi, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Gl-Go, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Gra, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Gre-Gw, 1799. (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - Hac-Han, 1799. (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Har, 1799. (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Haw-Hay, 1799. (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - He, 1799. (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Hi, 1799. (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Hol-Hop, 1799. (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Hor-Hoy, 1799. (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Hu, 1799. (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - I, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Ja-Je, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - John-Johnson, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Johnston, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Jon-Ju, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Ke, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Ki, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - King, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Kn-Ky, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - La-Le, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - Li-Lu, 1799. (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - McB-McC, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - McC-McG, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - McK-McR, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Mab-Mal, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Man-Mar, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Mas-Maz, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Me, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Mi, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Miller, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Mon-Moo, 1799. (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - Mor, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Mu, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - N, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Nathan, Simon, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - O, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Pa, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Pea-Pen, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 7)